ILGWU Education Department Publications 5780/166 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Starr, Mark. Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.2, 1937-1944; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: New Europe and America, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from The Left News, April, 1942. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Cleavages? Yes. Panel Cites Community Problems, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Mark Starr. In Journal League Magazine, June, 1942. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Very Brittle. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The I.L.G.W.U. Program: Twenty-Five Years of Workers Education, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Mark Starr. In The Lithographers Journal, v.27:no.5 (1942:Aug.). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Labor Needs Learning... and Vice Versa, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Frontiers of Democracy, October 15, 1942. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: What Should Schools Teach About Unionism?, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from the Harvard Educational Review, v.12:no.4 (1942:Oct.). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Role of Labor in the War Effort, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Social Education, v.7:no.4 (1943:April). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Workers' Education, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from American Federationist, June, 1943. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Labor Looks at Migration, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Mark Starr. In Current History, December, 1943. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Challenges to American Youth, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from New Leader, July 24, 1943. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Employers Get Unions They Deserve, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Mark Starr. In Workers' Education News, v.23:no.1 (1944:Jan. 15). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Educational Work of the ILGWU, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Journal of Adult Education, January, 1937. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Worker, His Union, and the Public Schools, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Progressive Education, January, 1942. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Labor as Equal Partner, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Starr, Mark. Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3, 1945-1948; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  English and German
  - Item 1: Labor in the Atomic Era, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Mark Starr. In Labour and Learning, November, 1945. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Economic Life and Individual Freedom, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Mark Starr. In The Standard, v.32:no.2 (1945:Nov.). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Purging the Text Books, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from The New Republic, December 31, 1945. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Planning for Freedom, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Mark Starr. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Unions Fight Jim Crow and Racism, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Education, January, 1946. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Democracy in Trade Unions, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Phillip Taft. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Librarians and Labor, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Library Journal, March 15, 1946. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Struggles for Industrial Power, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Education for Labor, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Vocational Education and Unesco, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Viewpoint, May, 1946. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Biography of Mark Starr, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    In Current Biography, v.7:no.7 (1946:July). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: The Movement Nobody Knows, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Current History, July, 1946. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Labor Looks at Education, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Mark Starr. In The Education Digest, v.12:no.4 (1946:Dec.). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Japan's Labor Unions, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Forum, February, 1947. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Where Coal and Blood Are Buried., Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Mark Starr. Book Review in Saturday Review of Literature, v.30:no.19 (1947:May 10). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Guide for House Call Committees., Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: The Pains of Private Enterprise, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Mark Starr. In the Workmen's Circle Call, v.13:no.5 (1945:July). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: British Labor Takes Power, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Mark Starr. In Common Sense, September, 1945. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Training for Union Service, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Mark Starr. In The Canadian Unionist, v.21:no.6 (1947:June). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Esperanto in Japan, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Mark Starr. Letter in New York Times, October 2, 1947. Photocopy. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Gewerkschaftsfuhrer, wie sie sein sollen, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Mark Starr. In Gewerkschaftliche Nachrichten, no.2 (1948:Sept. 29). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in German.
  - Item 22: A Union View: II, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Mark Starr. In Operating Under the LMRA: Relation of Wages to Productivity. Personnel Series no.122. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: What Should the Administration Do About the High Cost of Living, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Mark Starr; Hubert H. Humphrey; Ralph E. Flanders; Herman W. Steinkraus; George V. Denny, Jr. In Town Meeting, v.14:no.29 (1948:Nov. 16). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Record of Organized Labor, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    By Mark Starr. Letter to Editor, December, 1949. Photocopy. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.3. Item is in English.
- Starr, Mark. Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.4, 1948-1950; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Labor's Concern With Adult Education, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Mark Starr. Chapter 5 in The Community Responsibilities of Institutions of Higher Education. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.4. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The Negro's Stake in the Future of American Industry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Mark Starr. Address delivered to the National Urban League Conference, 1948. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.4. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Why Union Education? Aims, History, and Philosophy of the Educational Work of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from the Proceedings of the American Philosophical Society, v.92:no.3 (1948). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.4, Second copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Museums and the Labor Unions, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Mark Starr. In Museum News, v.26:no.13 (1949:Jan. 1). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.4. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Closed Minds Are Dead Minds, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from News Bulletin, February, 1949. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.4. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: First Semiannual Report of all Educational Exchange Activities Carried on from July 1 to December 31, 1948, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Mark Starr; Harvie Branscomb; Karl Taylor; Harold Willis Dodds, Martin R. P. McGuire. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.4. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Union Label Welfare Work, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Mark Starr. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.4. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Labor Through Polls, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Mark Starr. In The Labor Zionist, v4:no.4 (1949:March 18). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.4. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Building and Defending Democracy: The Role of Workers' Education, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from The Educational Forum, March, 1949. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.4. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Proceedings of the Third Labor-Management Round-Table, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Mark Starr. April 29, 1949. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.4. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Third Annual Labor-Management Round-Table Conference Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Mark Starr. April 29-30, 1949. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.4. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Re: "Education in Industrial and Labor Relations", Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Industrial and Labor Relations Review, v.3:no.4 (1950:July). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.4. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Union Education for Leisure: A summary of educational and recreational facilities provided by ILGWU-AFL for its members, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By David Dubinsky. Reprinted from Education, October, 1950. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.4. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Operation: Trade Union Education, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Teachers College Record, v.52:no.2 (1950:Nov.). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.4. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Union Teacher, Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    By Beulah Amidon. Reprinted from The Survey, December, 1950. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.4. Item is in English.
- Starr, Mark. Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.5, 1951-1953; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: In the Beginning: The Word, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Mark Starr. In ALA Bulletin, v.45:no.7 (1951:July-Aug.). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.5. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labor in Educational Exchange, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Mark Starr. In The Record: Department of State International Exchange, v.7:no.4 (1951:July-Aug.). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.5. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Bevin and Morrison, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Mark Starr. In Institute of Social Studies Bulletin, v.1:no.3 (1951:Oct.). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.5. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Workers' Education, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Harvard Educational Review, v.21:no.4 (1951:Fall). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.5. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: John Dewey Attacked by the Communists, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Progressive Education, v.29:no.2 (1951:Nov.). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.5. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Toward Working, Creative Unity, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Mark Starr. In To Strengthen World Freedom. Special Publications Series no.1. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.5. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Why, What and How Teach Youth About Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Education, April, 1952. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.5. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: What the Citizen Should Know About Labor, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Machinists Monthly Journal, May, 1952. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.5. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: "Public Affairs Pamphlets" A Teaching Tool to Match Today's problems, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from The American Teacher, November, 1952. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.5. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: The Basis of World Organization and Labor's Contribution to International Understanding, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Mark Starr. Chapter 12 from Foundations of World Organization: A Political and Cultural Appraisal. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.5. Second copy. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Labor's Stake in Public Education, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Mark Starr. Lecture presented to the Sixth Session 1952-53 School Board Institute on Public Education, May 6, 1953. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.5. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Living a Faith Without Dogma, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Mark Starr. In The Standard, v.39:no.5 (1953:June-July). From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.5. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Moral Standards in Business and Labor, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Mark Starr. Conference on Moral Standards, September 13-15, 1953. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.5. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Speech Problems in Labor-Management Relations, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Today's Speech, October, 1953. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.5. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Hands Across Frontiers, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Mark Starr. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.5. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Labor Fights Bigotry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Prophetic Religion. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.5. Item is in English.
- Starr, Mark. Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.6, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Labor's Coming of Age, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    By Mark Starr. Chapter 15 in Wellsprings of the American Spirit. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.6. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Let's Put More Life Into Union Meetings, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from American Federationist. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.6. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The Negro's Stake in the Future of American Industry, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    By Mark Starr. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.6. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Socialism': Is It a Smear Word Or a Menace?, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    By Mark Starr. Reprinted from Kenosha Labor. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.6. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Basis of World Organization and Labor's Contribution to International Understanding, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    By Mark Starr. Eleventh Conference on Science, Philosophy and Religion. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.6. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Freedom and Authority in Labor Unions, Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    By Mark Starr. Twelfth Conference on Science, Philosophy and Religion. From Newspaper and Magazine Articles. vol.6. Item is in English.
- Teper, Lazare. Activities of the I.L.G.W.U. Research Department., 1942; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  May 1942.
  - Item 1: Activities of the I.L.G.W.U. Research Department., Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    By Lazare Teper. Reprinted from Labor Information Bulletin, May, 1942. Second copy. Item is in English.
- Trade Union Educational League. Amalgamation., 1930; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Amalgamation., Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    By Jay Fox. Labor Herald Library no.5. Item is in English.
- Tyler, Gus and David Wells. Camel Bites Dachshund., 1961; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Camel Bites Dachshund., Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    By Gus Tyler; David Wells. Reprinted from The New Republic, November 27, 1961. Item is in English.
- Tyler, Gus. Report on Political, Educational, and Training Institute Departments., 1961; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  June 1961.
  - Item 1: Report on Political, Educational, and Training Institute Departments., Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    By Gus Tyler. June 1961.. Item is in English.
- U.S. Office of Defense Mobilization. Surplus Manpower Committee. Hearings on the Apparel Industry. [folder 1 of 2], 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Surplus Manpower Committee. Hearings on the Apparel Industry. [folder 1 of 2], Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    May, 1952. Item is in English.
- U.S. Office of Defense Mobilization. Surplus Manpower Committee. Hearings on the Apparel Industry. [folder 2 of 2], 1952; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Surplus Manpower Committee. Hearings on the Apparel Industry. [folder 2 of 2], Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
- USIS Feature. Training Union Officers: How the Garment Workers do it., 1965; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  July 1965.
  - Item 1: USIS Feature. Training Union Officers: How the Garment Workers do it., Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    July 1965. Item is in English.
- University and College Labor Education Association. Directory of Member Institutions and Professional Staff., 1979; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Directory of Member Institutions and Professional Staff., Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
- University of the State of New York State Education Department. Study of Vocational Education in NYC Schools., 1947; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Study of Vocational Education in NYC Schools., Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Uviller, Harry. The Efficiency Order Issued by the Impartial Chairman of the New York Dress Industry., 1941; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Efficiency Order Issued by the Impartial Chairman of the New York Dress Industry., Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    By Harry Uviller. Item is in English.
- Uviller, Harry. Impartial Machinery in the Dress Industry., 1949; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Impartial Machinery in the Dress Industry., Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    By Harry Uviller. Training for Trade Union Service. Second copy. Item is in English.
- Williams, Wylma A. What the ILGWU Means to Me., Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: What the ILGWU Means to Me., Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    By Wylma A. Williams. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- Workers Education Bureau of America. Workers Education., 1926-1936; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  v.3:no.4 (1926:Feb.); v.12:no.3 (1935:July); v.13:no.4 (1936:Oct.)
  - Item 1: Workers Education., Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    v.3:no.4 (1926:Feb.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Workers Education., Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    v.12:no.3 (1935:July). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Workers Education., Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    v.13:no.4 (1936:Oct.). Item is in English.
- Yomen, Ben. Needles and Pins., 1941; Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Needles and Pins., Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
    By Ben Yomen. Cartoons, reprinted from Justice. Second copy. Item is in English.
- Ziskind, David. Labor Law Notes., 1950; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
  January 1950.
  - Item 1: Labor Law Notes., Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    By David Ziskind. January 1950. Item is in English.
- Thoughts on Learning by the Students of the ILGWU Worker-Family Education Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Thoughts on Learning by the Students of the ILGWU Worker-Family Education Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Students and Teachers: Partners Together, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Students and Teachers: Partners Together, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Students in Action, 1993-1994; Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
  English, Spanish, and Chinese. Site 218
  - Item 1: Students in Action, Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
    Site 218. Item is in English; Spanish; Chinese.
  - Item 2: Students in Action, Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Students in Action, 1994-1995; Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Students in Action, Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Item 2: Students in Action, Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Making a Living: What We Did, What We Do, What We Want To Do, Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Making a Living: What We Did, What We Do, What We Want To Do, Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
    By Worker-Family Education Program. Item is in English.
- The Rising Sun, 1994; Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
  Student magazine. 2 copies.
  - Item 1: The Rising Sun, Publication (Box 3, Folder 25)
    By Worker-Family Education Program. Student magazine. 2 copies. Item is in English.
- Rainbows, 1990; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
  Local 23-25. Chinatown Site
  - Item 1: Ranibows, Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    By Family-Worker Education Program. Local 23-25. Chinatown Site. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Rainbows, Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    By Worker-Family Education Program. Local 23-25. Chinatown Site. Item is in English.
- Rainbows, 1995; Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
  Local 23-25. Chinatown Site.
  - Item 1: Ranibows, Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Item 2: Rainbows, Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Hot Off the Press, 1990-1991; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  Local 155
  - Item 1: Hot Off the Press, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    By Worker-Family Education Program. Local 155. Item is in English.
- We've Come a Long Way Baby, 1989; Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: We've Come a Long Way Baby, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Nuestra Familia, Trabajo y Educacion, 1994; Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
  Spanish. vol. 1
  - Item 1: Nuestra Familia, Trabajo y Educacion, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    By Worker-Family Education Program. vol. 1. Item is in Spanish.
- Student Magazine, 1987-1988; Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Student Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
    By Worker-family Education Program. Item is in English.
- Our Mural of Cultures, 1990; Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Our Mural of Cultures, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Oral Histories: The Words, A Class Project, 1989; Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Oral Histories: The Words, A Class Project, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)